# Laura Ordaz

# Office Manager, Bookkeeper, Adminiatrative Assistant, Human Resources, Life Insurance Agent

Lodi, CA lauraordaz4\_9bo@indeedemail.com (209) 747-2614

To strive to be a valuable asset to your company by using my skills acquired by my work experience.

## Work Experience

#### **Bookkeeper/Admin Assistant**

JBT Property Management - Lodi, CA September 2018 to 2019

Bookkeeping for multiple entities

Working with remote Executives & Customers

Quickbooks online

**Bank Reconciliations** 

Workers Comp Report

Accounts Payable and Receivable

**Excel Reports** 

Payroll

Some month and year end reporting

Some tax preparation

Working with OnSite/RealPage

Keeping Google Drive & Office 365 virtual filing

Administrative Duties

Office Management

**HR Duties** 

#### **Life Insurance Agent**

New York Life

June 2016 to May 2017

Networking

Cold Calling

**Event Planning** 

Scheduling

Meeting with clients and potential clients

Assessing needs and providing best solutions

## Office Manager

Solar City - Stockton, CA April 2013 to June 2016

Responsibilities

# Human Resources

- # Payroll
- # Expense Reports
- # Data Entry
- # Excel Reports

Fleet Management

# Travel Arrangements

Direct assistant to the Operatiins Manager

Assisting Warehouse and sales managers

- # Managing office staff & installers
- # A/P & A/R
- # Marinating Office budget

## **Office Manager**

Synergy Companies - Lodi, CA February 2012 to April 2013

- # Human Resources
- # OuickBooks
- # Administrating Energy Upgrade California Energy Upgrade CA Program
- # Energy Upgrade California Rebates
- # Job Scheduling
- # Telemarketing
- # Invoicing & A/R
- # Managing office staff & technicians
- # Working with different financing programs

## **Administrative Assistant / Sales Rep**

Chappell Transport Inc - Lodi, CA October 2007 to May 2011

- # A/P and A/R
- # Quick books
- # Answering Phones and Customer Service
- # Light Dispatching
- # Invoices and Billing
- # Bookkeeping
- # Payroll
- # Sales Rep at Car Auctions
- # General Office Work

#### Receptionist

Wood Crafters Inc - Acampo, CA April 2007 to September 2007

- # Answering Phones
- # Posting Bills, Invoices, Purchase Orders, Entering Time Cards
- # Ordering Materials and Supplies

#### Clerk II

CB Merchant Services - Stockton, CA

## April 2002 to April 2006

- # Data Entry, Answering Phones, Customer Service
- # Taking /Posting payments, Calling Clients, Skip Tracing
- # Verifying Information/ References

## Education

# High school or equivalent

## Skills

- Quickbooks
- Bookkeeping
- Accounts Payable
- Microsoft Office (10+ years)
- Accounts Receivable
- Onsite/ Real Page
- Google Docs
- Office 365

## Certifications and Licenses

## **Notary Public**

## Additional Information

#### Skill Profile:

•Bookkeeping, Human Resources, QuickBooks, Excel, Word, Outlook, Great Phone Etiquette